filipinastvtambayan.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Your privacy matters to us.

The types of information we collect:

Filipinastvtambayan.com collects the following types of information:

1\. Registration/contact information. When you register to watch videos on Filipinastvtambayan.com, we collect your email address. We use this information to contact you for lost username or password purposes and to inform you about Site services in which you’ve expressed interest.

2\. Profile Information. Filipinastvtambayan.com users have the ability to voluntarily create and modify their user profile using the ” My Profile” menu. The information collected, such as name, age, sex and location is displayed to other users and is completely voluntary. Filipinastvtambayan.com does not require users to create a user profile.

3\. No information specific to a user’s personal identity is ever revealed unless the user “opts-in” to receive other specific information such as partner and advertiser offers.

4\. The information you supply to us when you are registering and setting up your personal Filipinastvtambayan.com account is used to provide our basic services. Because we store your personal information, we don’t have to ask you to re-register each time you want to access the site. Filipinastvtambayan.com routinely sends all new members a welcoming email to verify their passwords and user names.

Filipinastvtambayan.com may, at times, share aggregate statistical information about our members with business partners, sponsors and other affiliates. For example, we may share our findings that the Filipinastvtambayan.com audience watches videos x hours per week. This information is aggregated and will not personally identify our members.

However, Filipinastvtambayan.com may disclose personal information for the following business or legal reasons:

In special cases. When we have reason to believe, for example, that disclosing this information may help to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who, intentionally or unintentionally, may be causing injury or interference with Filipinastvtambayan.com’s rights or property, other Filipinastvtambayan.com members, or anyone else who might be harmed as a result.

Collection and use of members’ IP addresses

An IP address is a number that’s automatically assigned to your computer whenever you surf the Web. Web servers automatically identify your computer by its IP address.

Filipinastvtambayan.com collects IP addresses to analyze trends, administer our site, anonymously track members’ movements on our site, and to gather broad demographic information for statistical purposes. When guests request pages from the Site, our servers log those guests’ IP addresses. We do not link IP addresses to any personal information, so that while a member’s session will be logged, the member remains anonymous – to us, and to anyone else.

We use IP addresses in only a few types of situations. We may use these addresses to identify a member when it’s necessary to enforce compliance with our policies or terms of service, or to protect our service, Site, customers or others. We may also use these addresses to capture time stamps so that we can determine peak and off-peak load times. These addresses may also be used to determine browser type for demographic information.

Your acceptance of this privacy policy

By using the Site, you indicate your agreement with the terms and conditions of this privacy policy. If you do not agree with this privacy policy, then do not use the Site. We reserve the right to change the terms of this privacy policy. We will notify you of any material changes to this policy via email or by posting a prominent notice on the Site stating that the privacy policy has been updated. We will give you an opportunity to “opt out” of having your information collected and used pursuant to this materially different privacy policy. Also, we encourage you to review this privacy policy on a regular basis.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

DoubleClick DART cookie:

(1) Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.  
(2) Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to these sites and other sites on the Internet.  
(3) Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

DMCA

Filipinastvtambayan.com takes matters of Intellectual Property very seriously and is committed to meeting the needs of content owners while helping them manage publication of their content online. It should be noted that Filipinastvtambayan.com is a simple search engine of videos available at a wide variety of third party websites.

Any videos shown on third party websites are the responsibility of those sites and not Filipinastvtambayan.com. We have no knowledge of whether content shown on third party websites is or is not authorized by the content owner as that is a matter between the host site and the content owner. Filipinastvtambayan.com does not host any content on its servers or network.

Content Owners can use the DMCA protocol to request removal of links to videos that they believe infringe their copyright.  
Content owners must understand that by having a link removed from Filipinastvtambayan.com they will not be removing the actual source video from the 3rd party site. Content owners must contact the video hosting site themselves to request removal.  
Content owners must also understand that Filipinastvtambayan.com is a complex system of automatic indexers, robotic scripts and user submissions; if a video exists on the web we will at some point find it and index it. It is entirely possible that we will index a previously removed video that is hosted using a different URL or different hosting website. If this happens please let us know as per DMCA protocol and we will address the issue.

If you wish to request multiple link removals please use one DMCA notice but list all the URLS in that request. Once a link is removed we will blacklist that URL so that it may never again be posted to Filipinastvtambayan.com.

We aim to act on a DMCA request within 72 hours of receiving notification, however if we received your request we will take action to it immediately.

Digital Millennium Copyright Act of 1998

In accordance with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act of 1998 (the text of which may be found on the U.S. Copyright Office website at lcweb.loc.gov/copyright), Filipinastvtambayan.com will respond expeditiously to claims of copyright infringement that are reported to Filipinastvtambayan.com’s designated copyright agent identified below.

If you are a copyright owner, or are authorized to act on behalf of an owner of the copyright or of any exclusive right under the copyright, and believe that your work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please report your notice of infringement to Filipinastvtambayan.com by providing Filipinastvtambayan.com’s designated copyright agent listed below with the following information:

1\. A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed;  
2\. Identification of the copyright work claimed to have been infringed, or, if multiple copyrighted works at a single online site are covered by a single notification, a representative list of such works at the Website;  
3\. Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled, and information reasonably sufficient to permit Filipinastvtambayan.com to locate the material; this must be in the form of a direct URL to the page on which the infringing content is linked. This detail is necessary as each video can have multiple links and to protect relationships with our partners we wish to avoid deleting authorized links in error.  
4\. Information reasonably sufficient to permit Filipinastvtambayan.com to contact the complaining party, including a name, address, telephone number and, if available, an email address at which the complaining party may be contacted;  
5\. A statement that the complaining party has a good-faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent or the law; and  
6\. A statement that the information in the notification is accurate and, under penalty of perjury, that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.

All claims of copyright infringement on or regarding this Website should be emailed to Filipinastvtambayan.com designated agent at: Filipinastvtambayan@gmail.com
